Don't you think we should just go back?
ألا تعتقد أنه يجب علينا العودة؟
We'll get caught.
سيتم القبض علينا.
No way.
مستحيل.
It's my first date with you, after all.
إنه موعدي الأول معك، بعد كل شيء.
Besides, it's fine.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، فهو جيد.
I've actually been here for work before.
لقد كنت هنا للعمل من قبل.
So, if anything happens, I can just ask for help.
لذا، إذا حدث أي شيء، يمكنني فقط أن أطلب المساعدة.
Come, Matsuri.
تعال يا ماتسوري.
- It's beautiful, isn't it? - Amazing.
- إنه جميل، أليس كذلك؟ - مذهل.
- So cute! - So pretty.
- لطيف جدًا! - جميل جدًا.
It's really cute, right?
إنه لطيف حقًا، أليس كذلك؟
­
­
I watched a show here for the first time when I was a kid.
لقد شاهدت عرضًا هنا لأول مرة عندما كنت طفلاً.
Haruka and Rihito were with me.
وكان هاروكا ورييهيتو معي.
Really, is that so?
هل هذا صحيح حقا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
And I was really fascinated by it.
لقد كنت مفتونًا به حقًا.
They looked so cool as they performed and had all eyes on them.
لقد بدوا رائعين للغاية أثناء أدائهم وكانت كل العيون عليهم.
I wanted to be someone who can captivate others like that.
أردت أن أكون شخصًا قادرًا على جذب انتباه الآخرين مثله.
And that was that?
وذاك كان ذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's probably what inspired me to become an idol.
ربما هذا هو ما ألهمني لأصبح صنمًا.
Wow...
رائع...
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Yes?
نعم؟
I know it's very impolite to ask for such a thing.
أعرف أنه من غير المهذب أن أطلب مثل هذا الشيء.
But the actor playing the prince in today's show is unwell.
لكن الممثل الذي يلعب دور الأمير في عرض اليوم مريض.
We're having trouble finding a substitute.
نحن نواجه مشكلة في العثور على بديل.
Ah, alright.
اه، حسنا.
Huh?
هاه؟
Oh, never mind. I'm really sorry.
أوه، لا بأس. أنا آسف حقًا.
I don't mean to cause you trouble.
لا أقصد أن أسبب لك مشاكل.
Please ignore what I said.
من فضلك تجاهل ما قلته.
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
If you'll take me.
إذا كنت ستأخذني.
Would you, really?
هل ستفعل ذلك حقا؟
Want to watch me perform the role of prince?
هل تريد أن تشاهدني أؤدي دور الأمير؟
­
­
You look so cool!
تبدو رائعا جدا!
Watch me closely.
انظر إلي عن كثب.
I'll show you who's the coolest prince in the world.
سأريكم من هو الأمير الأكثر روعة في العالم.
Okay.
تمام.
I apologize for the trouble during your precious time with your sister.
أعتذر عن الإزعاج أثناء وقتك الثمين الذي تقضيه مع أختك.
Right.
يمين.
May I ask for one selfish favor in exchange for doing this?
هل يجوز لي أن أطلب معروفًا أنانيًا واحدًا مقابل القيام بهذا؟
No, no, no!
لا، لا، لا!
Let's go, Matsuri!
دعنا نذهب، ماتسوري!
You should be the one performing. Why me?
يجب أن تكون أنت من يؤدي. لماذا أنا؟
Look at their faces.
أنظر إلى وجوههم.
Wow! It's Cinderella!
واو! إنها سندريلا!
A prince and a princess!
أمير وأميرة!
Is this the world you guys always see?
هل هذا هو العالم الذي ترونه دائمًا؟
Yes, it is.
نعم إنه كذلك.
I don't know of any view better than this.
لا أعرف أي وجهة نظر أفضل من هذا.
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
I have feelings for you...
لدي مشاعر تجاهك...
not as a sister, but as a romantic...
ليس كأخت، بل كشخص رومانسي...
­credits
الاعتمادات
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I wanted to hear your confession all the way through, but I couldn't wait.
لقد أردت أن أسمع اعترافك حتى النهاية، لكنني لم أستطع الانتظار.
I love you.
أحبك.
Oh no, I accidentally said it.
أوه لا، لقد قلت ذلك عن طريق الخطأ.
I've lost my mind.
لقد فقدت عقلي.
And also...
و أيضا...
Oh no!
أوه لا!
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Good morning, I'm heading to school early. See you!
صباح الخير، سأذهب إلى المدرسة باكرًا. إلى اللقاء!
[Come to the nurse's office]
[تعال إلى مكتب الممرضة]
Finally, you came closer.
أخيرا، لقد اقتربت.
Wait, were you pretending to sleep?
انتظر، هل كنت تتظاهر بالنوم؟
And that note?
وتلك المذكرة؟
Why are you trying to run away?
لماذا تحاول الهرب؟
Because...
لأن...
At least tell me why.
على الأقل أخبرني لماذا.
Because it's not working like a normal romance.
لأنه لا يعمل مثل الرومانسية العادية.
What?
ماذا؟
We aren't like an idol and a fan, nor like siblings.
نحن لسنا مثل المعبود والمعجب، ولا مثل الأشقاء.
I don't know how to talk to you.
لا أعرف كيف أتحدث معك.
How long have you been a fan of Terzetto?
منذ متى وأنت من محبي Terzetto؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Since your debut, about three years.
منذ ظهورك لأول مرة، منذ حوالي ثلاث سنوات.
And a month since we became siblings.
ومرت شهر منذ أن أصبحنا أشقاء.
Yup.
نعم.
But as a couple, just one day.
لكن كزوجين، يوم واحد فقط.
So, one month ago, just like when we first became siblings,
لذا، منذ شهر واحد، تمامًا كما حدث عندما أصبحنا أشقاء لأول مرة،
let's start over from a distance just close enough to hold hands.
دعونا نبدأ من جديد من مسافة قريبة بما يكفي لمسك الأيدي.
We can take it slow, Matsuri.
يمكننا أن نأخذ الأمر ببطء، ماتسوري.
Nice to meet you again.
يسعدني أن ألتقي بك مرة أخرى.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
This much is just fine.
هذا جيد تمامًا.
Matsuri!
ماتسوري!
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I remember you.
انا اتذكرك.
You are the...
أنت...
If you don't want to be on the cover of a weekly magazine,
إذا كنت لا تريد أن تكون على غلاف مجلة أسبوعية،
hang out with me, will you, little sister?
هل يمكنك أن تتواجد معي يا أختي الصغيرة؟
Huh?
هاه؟
You're Misuzu Yamato, the dancer and idol, right?
أنت ميسوزو ياماتو، الراقصة والمعبودة، أليس كذلك؟
Why do you have that photo of us?
لماذا لديك تلك الصورة لنا؟
I'm glad you know about me.
يسعدني أنك تعرفني.
Nice to meet you, new student.
يسعدني أن أقابلك، أيها الطالب الجديد.
Could you please delete that photo?
هل بإمكانك حذف هذه الصورة من فضلك؟
You're desperate, huh?
أنت يائس، أليس كذلك؟
Wow, the cool second son of Terzetto, Azusa, is dating his sister. Oh my...
يا إلهي، أزوسا، الابن الثاني الرائع لتيرزيتو، يواعد أخته. يا إلهي...
That's not true!
هذا ليس صحيحا!
Azusa is my brother.
أزوسا هو أخي.
Nothing more, nothing less.
لا أكثر ولا أقل.
What would it take for you to delete it?
ماذا يتطلب الأمر لحذفه؟
[PRISM]
[موشور]
It's Subaru.
إنها سوبارو.
We're going to make our debut.
نحن سنقوم بأول ظهور لنا.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Subaru, he...
سوبارو، هو...
He's completely into you, right?
إنه معجب بك تمامًا، أليس كذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
I'm so interested.
أنا مهتم جدًا.
I wonder how impressive you must be to make our top ace so captivated.
أتساءل كيف يجب أن تكون مثيرا للإعجاب لتجعل أفضل لاعب لدينا مفتونًا بهذا.
So...
لذا...
Let's pretend to be a couple.
دعونا نتظاهر بأننا زوجين.
- What? - Let's go.
- ماذا؟ - لنذهب.
Is it fun?
هل هو ممتع؟
Not really for me.
ليس بالنسبة لي حقا.
I'm having fun. Do you need to use the restroom?
أنا أستمتع. هل تحتاج إلى استخدام الحمام؟
No, I'm fine.
لا، أنا بخير.
Yamato, why are you with this transfer student?
ياماتو، لماذا أنت مع هذا الطالب المنقول؟
This girl? She's my girlfriend.
هذه الفتاة؟ إنها صديقتي.
And the little sister of Terzetto.
والأخت الصغيرة لتيرزيتو.
Hey, Yamato.
مهلا، ياماتو.
- That girl is Terzetto's sister? - Ah, I made a mistake.
- تلك الفتاة هي أخت تيرزيتو؟ - آه، لقد ارتكبت خطأ.
- I said it, sorry. - So it's true.
- قلت ذلك، آسف. - إذن فهو صحيح.
But aren't their genetics too different?
ولكن أليست جيناتهم مختلفة جدًا؟
I heard they are step siblings.
سمعت أنهم أخوة غير أشقاء.
Honey.
عسل.
Hey, honey.
مرحبا عزيزتي.
This had to happen right when I was thinking about making friends.
كان لا بد أن يحدث هذا في الوقت الذي كنت أفكر فيه في تكوين صداقات.
Here you are, honey.
أنت هنا يا عزيزتي.
This guy is bad news.
هذا الرجل أخبار سيئة.
Hey! What's this?
مهلا! ما هذا؟
Aren't we dating?
ألسنا متواعدين؟
Pretending as lovers with me seems pointless, doesn't it?
يبدو أن التظاهر بالحب معي لا معنى له، أليس كذلك؟
Yeah, you're right.
نعم، أنت على حق.
It's probably not as fun as I expected.
ربما لم يكن الأمر ممتعًا كما توقعت.
This "pastime".
هذه "الهواية".
Jeez!
يا إلهي!
Hey, stop it already and delete the photos.
مهلا، توقف عن ذلك الآن واحذف الصور.
Because you're the girl Subaru likes,
لأنك الفتاة التي يحبها سوبارو،
I thought I might at least have a good time.
اعتقدت أنني قد أقضي وقتًا ممتعًا على الأقل.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Giving a good time isn't an easy task.
إن قضاء وقت ممتع ليس بالمهمة السهلة.
But idols like you can do it, so you are special.
لكن الأصنام مثلك قادرة على فعل ذلك، لذا فأنت مميزة.
Because you are good entertainers.
لأنكم فنانين جيدين.
Only idols can do something like that.
لا يمكن إلا للأصنام أن تفعل شيئًا كهذا.
You're alright.
أنت بخير.
Your secret got out and I made fun of you,
لقد انكشف سرك وسخرت منك،
and you still compliment me like that?
ومازلت تمدحني بهذه الطريقة؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Well, that was unexpected.
حسنًا، كان ذلك غير متوقع.
I feel a bit embarrassed.
أشعر بالحرج قليلاً.
I see, you think idols are special, huh?
أرى أنك تعتقد أن الأصنام خاصة، أليس كذلك؟
Fine, I'll delete it.
حسنًا، سأحذفه.
[Delete the selected images?]
[حذف الصور المحددة؟]
[The images have been deleted.]
[تم حذف الصور.]
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I don't really understand, but it's all right.
أنا لا أفهم حقًا، ولكن لا بأس.
While we're at it, should I give you a chance?
وبينما نحن في هذا الشأن، هل يجب أن أعطيك فرصة؟
A chance?
فرصة؟
Say, would you like to make an appearance in the music video
قل هل ترغب في الظهور في الفيديو الموسيقي
for our debut song?
لأغنيتنا الأولى؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
The director was looking for a girl.
وكان المخرج يبحث عن فتاة.
Someone ordinary like you.
شخص عادي مثلك.
Should I recommend you?
هل يجب أن أوصيك؟
What?
ماذا؟
Don't you want to prove everyone wrong?
ألا تريد أن تثبت أن الجميع مخطئون؟
Everyone at school.
الجميع في المدرسة.
And why would you want me at all?
ولماذا تريدني على الإطلاق؟
It's weird for someone like me to show up in your video, don't you think?
من الغريب أن يظهر شخص مثلي في الفيديو الخاص بك، ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
Sorry for spilling your secret, but you understand, right?
آسف لإفشال سرّك، لكنك تفهم، أليس كذلك؟
Understand what?
فهم ماذا؟
The reason for silly gossip is being surrounded by princes,
السبب وراء الثرثرة السخيفة هو التواجد بين الأمراء،
but not being able to be one.
ولكن لا أستطيع أن أكون واحدا منهم.
Give it a try.
جربها.
Isn't this a good chance?
أليس هذه فرصة جيدة؟
Being the co-star in Prism's music video...
كونه الممثل المشارك في الفيديو الموسيقي لـ Prism ...
Yeah.
نعم.
Don't worry, I'll turn down Subaru for you.
لا تقلق، سأرفض سوبارو من أجلك.
Actually, this didn't come from Subaru at all.
في الواقع، هذا لم يأتي من سوبارو على الإطلاق.
Besides, I want to give it a try.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، أريد أن أجربه.
Why? You don't need to.
لماذا؟ لا داعي لذلك.
Because if I do, I'll just embarrass myself?
لأنه إذا فعلت ذلك، سأحرج نفسي فقط؟
No, that's not it.
لا، ليس هذا هو الأمر.
Azusa, I feel like I can't just stay like this.
أزوسا، أشعر وكأنني لا أستطيع البقاء على هذا النحو.
I've realized that
لقد أدركت ذلك
I can't be proud of being the Terzetto sister as I am now.
لا أستطيع أن أكون فخورة بكوني أخت تيرزيتو كما أنا الآن.
And why would you choose the Prism music video for this out of all?
ولماذا اخترت فيديو كليب أغنية Prism لهذا العام من بين كل الفيديوهات؟
I've never thought of you as ordinary.
لم أفكر فيك أبدًا كشخص عادي.
So even if it's not what I want,
لذلك حتى لو لم يكن هذا ما أريده،
just go for it, if that's how you feel.
فقط اذهب لذلك، إذا كان هذا ما تشعر به.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Hey, what are you sneaking around for?
مهلا، لماذا تتسلل؟
I heard about it. It's a big deal for my sister.
سمعتُ عنه. إنه أمرٌ جللٌ لأختي.
Let's cheer for her.
دعونا نشجعها.
I'm going to be really worried about you, you know.
سأكون قلقًا جدًا عليك، كما تعلم.
Don't worry, nobody is going to devour me.
لا تقلق، لا أحد سوف يلتهمني.
Well, I'm not so sure about those Prism folks. Who knows what they'll do?
حسنًا، لست متأكدًا تمامًا بشأن هؤلاء الأشخاص من Prism. من يعلم ماذا سيفعلون؟
Wish I could just keep you here safely forever.
أتمنى أن أتمكن من إبقاءك هنا بأمان إلى الأبد.
But Matsuri, do your best.
لكن ماتسوري، افعلي ما بوسعك.
Don't forget, you're important to us.
لا تنسى أنك مهم بالنسبة لنا.
Yup.
نعم.
This might be foolish.
ربما يكون هذا حماقة.
But I want to be someone suitable for Terzetto.
لكنني أريد أن أكون شخصًا مناسبًا لـ Terzetto.
And I want to match up to Azusa.
وأريد أن أقابل أزوسا.
Hey.
يا.
- You're here. - You're our partner, you know?
- أنت هنا. - أنت شريكنا، هل تعلم؟
Despite being an amateur, you took it on really well.
على الرغم من كونك هاويًا، فقد تعاملت مع الأمر بشكل جيد حقًا.
Huh?
هاه؟
You're so naive.
أنت ساذج جدًا.
But don't worry about it.
ولكن لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
I won't be mean today.
لن أكون سيئا اليوم.
I'll see you later.
سوف أراك لاحقا.
He's a demon!
إنه شيطان!
Matsuri, are you okay?
ماتسوري، هل أنت بخير؟
Subaru!
سوبارو!
We'll take the lead, so all you have to do is just be there.
سنأخذ زمام المبادرة، لذلك كل ما عليك فعله هو مجرد التواجد هناك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
I'll give it my best.
سأبذل قصارى جهدي.
Don't forget that I'm the one you love the most in the world.
لا تنسى أنني الشخص الذي تحبه أكثر في العالم.
What? Hold on.
ماذا؟ انتظر.
Let's go and kill it out there.
دعونا نذهب ونقتله هناك.
Here's to our princess.
إلى أميرتنا.
You guys playing the princes compete for the princess.
أنتم يا رفاق الذين تلعبون دور الأمراء تتنافسون على الأميرة.
Let all the girls experience the moment of being wooed by their favorite idol
دع جميع الفتيات يختبرن لحظة جذب انتباه معبودهن المفضل
with all the passion on the screen.
مع كل العاطفة على الشاشة.
Let's make it an absolutely sensational debut!
دعونا نجعلها بداية مثيرة للغاية!
Ready, start!
جاهز، ابدأ!
I love you.
أحبك.
Come here, my princess.
تعالي هنا يا أميرتي.
You prefer quiet ones, don't you?
أنت تفضل الهدوء، أليس كذلك؟
Be mine?
كن لي؟
And in return, I'll give you everything of mine.
وفي المقابل سأعطيك كل ما أملك.
Hello, princess.
مرحباً يا أميرتي.
Your heart must be racing right before a kiss.
يجب أن يكون قلبك ينبض بسرعة قبل القبلة.
I love you.
أحبك.
Cut! OKay.
قطع! حسنا.
- Great job! - Thanks for the hard work.
- عمل رائع! - ​​شكرا على العمل الجاد.
Hey, thanks.
مرحبًا، شكرًا لك.
You did well.
لقد قمت بعمل جيد.
Your composure surprised me.
لقد فاجأني هدوؤك.
Thank you for doing this for Prism.
شكرا لك على القيام بهذا من أجل Prism.
No, thank you all very much.
لا، شكرا جزيلا لكم جميعا.
Matsuri.
ماتسوري.
Subaru.
سوبارو.
I'll come get you in real life too.
سوف آتي لأخذك إلى الحياة الحقيقية أيضًا.
It's finally done.
لقد تم ذلك أخيرا.
- Tired? - Yeah, I was nervous.
- متعب؟ - نعم، كنت متوترة.
I see.
أرى.
I'll work hard to become a girl who is worthy of you.
سأعمل بجد حتى أصبح الفتاة التي تستحقك.
Just like I always find you so cool,
تمامًا كما أجدك دائمًا رائعًا،
I want to become the kind of girl
أريد أن أصبح هذا النوع من الفتيات
who makes your heart race.
من يجعل قلبك ينبض بسرعة.
You don't know the real reason I didn't want you to be in the music video, do you?
أنت لا تعرف السبب الحقيقي لعدم رغبتي في وجودك في الفيديو الموسيقي، أليس كذلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
You don't need to be everyone's princess.
لا تحتاجين إلى أن تكوني أميرة الجميع.
It's enough if I'm the only prince for you.
يكفي أن أكون الأمير الوحيد بالنسبة لك.
I love you, Matsuri.
انا احبك ماتسوري.
(credits)
(الاعتمادات)
Listen carefully.
استمع بعناية.
The debut CD sales record held by Terzetto has been broken.
تم تحطيم الرقم القياسي لمبيعات أول ألبومات الألبوم الذي كان يحمله Terzetto.
- What? - Huh?
- ماذا؟ - هاه؟
By whom?
من قبل من؟
It's Prism.
إنه بريزم.
It's way ahead.
إنه الطريق إلى الأمام.
At this rate, Terzetto will be replaced by Prism.
بهذا المعدل، سيتم استبدال Terzetto بـ Prism.
­
­
It's flawless. [Prism's fresh faces in full swing!]
إنه لا تشوبه شائبة. [وجوه بريزم الجديدة في كامل نشاطها!]
You're seriously going at it.
أنت تُبدع حقًا. [وجوه بريزم الجديدة في كامل أناقتها!]
I'm not planning to give up on Matsuri.
أنا لا أخطط للتخلي عن ماتسوري.
Take a good look at me now. [Subaru and Matsuri, getting closer. What's next?]
انظر إليّ جيدًا الآن. [سوبارو وماتسوري يقتربان. ماذا بعد؟]
A hot spring trip as an appreciation party. [A thrilling hot spring trip]
رحلة ينابيع ساخنة كحفل تقدير. [رحلة ينابيع ساخنة مثيرة]
What? [Unexpected unisex bathing experience?]
ماذا؟ [تجربة استحمام غير متوقعة للجنسين؟]
Please don't go back to being an idol yet.
من فضلك لا تعود إلى كونك صنمًا بعد.